Guide to the Walt Horan Papers 1939-1967
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 2: Outgoing Office Correspondence, 1943-1964
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1950
    - P- July-December 1944 (Box 9, Folder 373)
    - P- January-April 1945 (Box 9, Folder 374)
    - P- May-September 1945 (Box 9, Folder 375)
    - P- October-December 1945 (Box 9, Folder 376)
    - P- January-February 1946 (Box 9, Folder 377)
    - P- March-May 18, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 378)
    - P- May 21-July 1946 (Box 9, Folder 379)
    - P- August-November 1946 (Box 9, Folder 380)
    - P- December 1946-February 8, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 381)
    - P- February 10-April 1947 (Box 9, Folder 382)
    - P- May-July 1947 (Box 9, Folder 383)
    - P- August-December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 384)
    - P- January 1948-March 1948 (Box 9, Folder 385)
    - P-April-July 1948 (Box 9, Folder 386)
    - P- August-December 1948 (Box 9, Folder 387)
    - P- January-March 17, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 388)
    - P- March 21-June 21, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 389)
    - P- June 22-November 8, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 390)
    - P- November 15, 1949-March 1950 (Box 9, Folder 391)
    - P- April-July 1950 (Box 9, Folder 392)
    - P- August-December 1950 (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - Q- November 1943-R June 15, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - R- June 18-November 1943 (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - R- December 1943-April 1944 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - R- May-December 1944 (Box 9, Folder 397)
    - R- January-June 14, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 398)
    - R- June 18-October 11, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 399)
    - R- October 15-December 1945 (Box 9, Folder 400)
    - R- January-March 9, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 401)
    - R- March 11-May 23, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - R- May 24-July 15, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - R- July 16-November 1946 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - R- December 1946-January 1947 (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - R- February-March 1947 (Box 9, Folder 406)
    - R- April-May 1947 (Box 9, Folder 407)
    - R- June-July 1947 (Box 9, Folder 408)
    - R- August-December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - R- January-March 4, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - R- March 5-May 5, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - R- May 7, 1848- September 1948 (Box 9, Folder 412)
    - R- October 1948-February 5, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 413)
    - R- February 7-April 9, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 414)
    - R- April 11-June 18, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 415)
    - R- June 20-September 1949 (Box 10, Folder 416)
    - R- October 1949-February 6, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 417)
    - R- February 8-May 1950 (Box 10, Folder 418)
    - R- June-September 11, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 419)
    - R- September 13-December 1950 (Box 10, Folder 420)
    - S- March-May 1943 (Box 10, Folder 421)
    - S- June-August 1943 (Box 10, Folder 422)
    - S- September-November 23, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 423)
    - S- November 24, 1943-January 25, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 424)
    - S- January 26-March 1944 (Box 10, Folder 425)
    - S- April-June 12, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 426)
    - S- June 13-October 1944 (Box 10, Folder 427)
    - S- November 1944-February 13, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 428)
    - S- February 14-April 19, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 429)
    - S- April 20-June 1945 (Box 10, Folder 430)
    - S- July-October 9, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 431)
    - S- October 10-November 14, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 432)
    - S- November 15-December 1945 (Box 10, Folder 433)
    - S- January-February 12, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 434)
    - S- February 13-March 8, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 435)
    - S- March 11-April 13, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 436)
    - S- April 15-May 17, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 437)
    - S- May 18-June 19, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 438)
    - S- June 20-August 16, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 439)
    - S- August 26-November 1946 (Box 10, Folder 440)
    - S- December 1946-January 1947 (Box 10, Folder 441)
    - S- February-March 5, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 442)
    - S- March 6-April 3, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 443)
    - S- April 7-May 7, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 444)
    - S- May 8- June 1947 (Box 10, Folder 445)
    - S-July-August 1947 (Box 10, Folder 446)
    - S- September-November 24, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 447)
    - S- November 25, 1947-January 21, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 448)
    - S- January 22-February 1948 (Box 10, Folder 449)
    - S- March 1948 (Box 10, Folder 450)
    - S- April-May 5, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 451)
    - S- May 6-June 9, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 452)
    - S- June 10-September 1948 (Box 10, Folder 453)
    - S- October-December 1948 (Box 10, Folder 454)
    - S- January-February 15, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 455)
    - S- February 16-March 17, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 456)
    - S- March 19-April 19, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 457)
    - S- April 20-June 10, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 458)
    - S- June 11- July 19, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 459)
    - S- July 21-September 1949 (Box 10, Folder 460)
    - S- October-November 1949 (Box 10, Folder 461)
    - S- December 1949-January 1950 (Box 10, Folder 462)
    - S- February-March 14, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 463)
    - S- March 15-May 23, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 464)
    - S- May 24-July 1950 (Box 10, Folder 465)
    - S- August-September 5, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 466)
    - S- September 6-November 5, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 467)
    - S- November 7-December 1950 (Box 10, Folder 468)
    - T- January-November 1943 (Box 10, Folder 469)
    - T- December 1943-August 1944 (Box 10, Folder 470)
    - T- September 1944-April 1945 (Box 10, Folder 471)
    - T- May-November 13, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 472)
    - T- November 15, 1945-March 1946 (Box 10, Folder 473)
    - T- April-July 1946 (Box 10, Folder 474)
    - T- August 1946-January 1947 (Box 10, Folder 475)
    - T- February-April 1947 (Box 10, Folder 476)
    - T- May-July 1947 (Box 10, Folder 477)
    - T- August 1947-January 1948 (Box 10, Folder 478)
    - T- February-May 3, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 479)
    - T- May 17-September 1948 (Box 10, Folder 480)
    - T- October 1948-February 1949 (Box 10, Folder 481)
    - T- March-June 17, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 482)
    - T- June 21-November 1949 (Box 11, Folder 483)
    - T- December 1949-April 6, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 484)
    - T- April 10-August 1950 (Box 11, Folder 485)
    - T- September-December 1950; U- May-February 1945 (Box 11, Folder 486)
    - U- March-April 1948 (Box 11, Folder 487)
    - U- June-December 1950; V- March-April 1944 (Box 11, Folder 488)
    - V- May 1944-December 1945 (Box 11, Folder 489)
    - V- January 1946-March 1947 (Box 11, Folder 490)
    - V- April 1947-May 1948 (Box 11, Folder 491)
    - V- June 1948-December 1950 (Box 11, Folder 492)
    - W-March-June 10, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 493)
    - W- June 11-October 1943 (Box 11, Folder 494)
    - W- November 1943-January 1944 (Box 11, Folder 495)
    - W- February-May 1944 (Box 11, Folder 496)
    - W- June-September 1944 (Box 11, Folder 497)
    - W- October 1944-January 1945 (Box 11, Folder 498)
    - W- February-April 1945 (Box 11, Folder 499)
    - W- May-July 10, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 500)
    - W- July 11-October 15, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 501)
    - W- October 16-November 1945 (Box 11, Folder 502)
    - W- December 1945-January 1946 (Box 11, Folder 503)
    - W- February-March 6, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 504)
    - W- March 7-April 18, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 505)
    - W- April 20-June 11, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 506)
    - W- June 12-July 1946 (Box 11, Folder 507)
    - W- August-October 16, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 508)
    - W- October 17-December 1946 (Box 11, Folder 509)
    - W- January-February 14, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 510)
    - W- February 18-April 9, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 511)
    - W- April 10-May 1947 (Box 11, Folder 512)
    - W- June-July 15, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 513)
    - W- July 16-November 10, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 514)
    - W- November 13-December 1947 (Box 11, Folder 515)
    - W- January-February 1948 (Box 11, Folder 516)
    - W- March-April 15, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 517)
    - W- April 19-June 8, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 518)
    - W- June 9-September 1948 (Box 11, Folder 519)
    - W- October-December 1948 (Box 11, Folder 520)
    - W- January-February 16, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 521)
    - W- February 17-April 5, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 522)
    - W- April 6-June 8, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 523)
    - W- June 11-August 10, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 524)
    - W- August 15-November 9, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 525)
    - W- November 14, 1949-February 14, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 526)
    - W- February 20-April 1950 (Box 11, Folder 527)
    - W- May-August 9, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 528)
    - W- August 14-November 5, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 529)
    - W- November 10-December 1950 (Box 11, Folder 530)
    - Y- March 1943-January 1947 (Box 11, Folder 531)
    - Y- February 1947-December 1950 (Box 11, Folder 532)
    - Z- January 1943-December 1946 (Box 11, Folder 533)
    - Z- January 1946-December 1950 (Box 11, Folder 534)
    - A- January 1951- May 1951 (Box 11, Folder 535)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1951-1953
    - A- June 1951-January 1952 (Box 11, Folder 536)
    - A- February-July 1952 (Box 11, Folder 537)
    - A- August-December 1952- B- January 19, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 538)
    - B- January 22-February 1951 (Box 11, Folder 539)
    - B- March-April 18, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 540)
    - B- April 21-June 11, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 541)
    - B- June 12- August 8, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 542)
    - B- August 13-October 1951 (Box 11, Folder 543)
    - B- November 1951-January 1952 (Box 11, Folder 544)
    - B- February-March 15, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 545)
    - B- March 18-May 6, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 546)
    - B- May 8-June 1952 (Box 11, Folder 547)
    - B- July-October 24, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 548)
    - B- October 25-December 1952 (Box 11, Folder 549)
    - C- January-February 15, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 550)
    - C- February 19-April 1951 (Box 12, Folder 551)
    - C- May-June 1951 (Box 12, Folder 552)
    - C- July-August 1951 (Box 12, Folder 553)
    - C- September-November 9, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 554)
    - C- November 14, 1951-January 1952 (Box 12, Folder 555)
    - C- February-March 15, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 556)
    - C- March 17- May 1952 (Box 12, Folder 557)
    - C- June-September 9, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 558)
    - C- September 10-December 1952 (Box 12, Folder 559)
    - D- January-April 10, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 560)
    - D- April 11-July 1951 (Box 12, Folder 561)
    - D- August-December 1951 (Box 12, Folder 562)
    - D- January-March 1952 (Box 12, Folder 563)
    - D- April-June 1952 (Box 12, Folder 564)
    - D- July-December 1952 (Box 12, Folder 565)
    - E- January-July 9, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 566)
    - E- July 12, 1951-March 5, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 567)
    - E- March 15-December 1952 (Box 12, Folder 568)
    - F- January 1951-April 1951 (Box 12, Folder 569)
    - F- May 1951- August 15, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 570)
    - F- August 16, 1951-February 1952 (Box 12, Folder 571)
    - F- March-June 6, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 572)
    - F- June 11-December 1952 (Box 12, Folder 573)
    - G- January-March 1951 (Box 12, Folder 574)
    - G- April-July 1951 (Box 12, Folder 575)
    - G- August-December 1951 (Box 12, Folder 576)
    - G- January-March 5, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 577)
    - G- March 11-July 15, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 578)
    - G- July 18-December 1952 (Box 12, Folder 579)
    - H- January-February 6, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 580)
    - H- February 7-March 6, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 581)
    - H- March 7-April 1951 (Box 12, Folder 582)
    - H- May-June 20, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 583)
    - H- June 21-August 14, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 584)
    - H- August 16-October 1951 (Box 12, Folder 585)
    - H- November 1951-January 18, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 586)
    - H- January 21-March 10, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 587)
    - H- March 11-April 1952 (Box 12, Folder 588)
    - H- May-June 1952 (Box 12, Folder 589)
    - H- July-October 1952 (Box 12, Folder 590)
    - H- November-December 1952- I- January 1951- December 1952 (Box 12, Folder 591)
    - J- January-April 1951 (Box 12, Folder 592)
    - J- May 1951-January 1952 (Box 12, Folder 593)
    - J- February-August 1952 (Box 12, Folder 594)
    - J- September-December 1952 (Box 12, Folder 595)
    - K- January-March 1951 (Box 12, Folder 596)
    - K- April-July 1951 (Box 12, Folder 597)
    - K- August 1951-February 1952 (Box 12, Folder 598)
    - K- March-July 1952 (Box 12, Folder 599)
    - K- August-December 1952 (Box 12, Folder 600)
    - L- January-March 9, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 601)
    - L- March 13-June 14, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 602)
    - L- June 18-September 14, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 603)
    - L- September 17-December 1951 (Box 12, Folder 604)
    - L- January-April 17, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 605)
    - L- April 22-September 9, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 606)
    - L- September 10-December 1952 (Box 12, Folder 607)
    - M- January-February 14, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 608)
    - M- February 15-March 1951 (Box 12, Folder 609)
    - M- April-May 17, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 610)
    - M- May 21-July 9, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 611)
    - M- July 11-September 14, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 612)
    - M- September 17-December 1951 (Box 12, Folder 613)
    - M- January-February 19, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 614)
    - M- February 20-March 1952 (Box 13, Folder 615)
    - M- April-May 1952 (Box 13, Folder 616)
    - M- June-July 1952 (Box 13, Folder 617)
    - M- August-November 10, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 618)
    - M- November 12-December 1952 (Box 13, Folder 619)
    - N- January-May 1951 (Box 13, Folder 620)
    - N- June 1951-March 1952 (Box 13, Folder 621)
    - N- April-December 1952 (Box 13, Folder 622)
    - O- January 1951-January 1952 (Box 13, Folder 623)
    - O- February-December 1952 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - P- January-March 1951 (Box 13, Folder 625)
    - P- April-June 1951 (Box 13, Folder 626)
    - P- July-October 15, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 627)
    - P- October 16, 1951-January 1952 (Box 13, Folder 628)
    - P- February-April 14, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 629)
    - P- April 15-August 1952 (Box 13, Folder 630)
    - P- September-December 1952; Q- January 1951-December 1952 (Box 13, Folder 631)
    - R- January-February 1951 (Box 13, Folder 632)
    - R- March-May 1951 (Box 13, Folder 633)
    - R- June-August 1951 (Box 13, Folder 634)
    - R- September 1951-January 1952 (Box 13, Folder 635)
    - R- February-March 1952 (Box 13, Folder 636)
    - R- April-June 1952 (Box 13, Folder 637)
    - R- July-December 1952 (Box 13, Folder 638)
    - S- January-February 9, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 639)
    - S- February 12-March 19, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 640)
    - S- March 20-May 15, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 641)
    - S- May 16-July 10, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 642)
    - S- July 11-August 20, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 643)
    - S- August 21-October 16, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 644)
    - S- October 18-December 1951 (Box 13, Folder 645)
    - S- January-February 18, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 646)
    - S- February 19-March 21, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 647)
    - S- March 25-May 14, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 648)
    - S- May 15-June 1952 (Box 13, Folder 649)
    - S- July-October 18, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 650)
    - S- October 21-December 1952 (Box 13, Folder 651)
    - T- January-March 1951 (Box 13, Folder 652)
    - T- April-July 1951 (Box 13, Folder 653)
    - T- August-December 1951 (Box 13, Folder 654)
    - T- January-April 1952 (Box 13, Folder 655)
    - T- May-September 1952 (Box 13, Folder 656)
    - T- October-December 1952; U- January-December 1952 (Box 13, Folder 657)
    - V- January 1951-December 1952 (Box 13, Folder 658)
    - W- January-February 15, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 659)
    - W- February 16-April 1951 (Box 13, Folder 660)
    - W- May-June 1951 (Box 13, Folder 661)
    - W- July-August 15, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 662)
    - W- August 16-November 1951 (Box 13, Folder 663)
    - W- December 1951-February 15, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 664)
    - W- February 19-May 15, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 665)
    - W- May 19-August 1952 (Box 13, Folder 666)
    - W- September-December 1952 (Box 13, Folder 667)
    - X, Y, Z- January 1951-December 1952 (Box 13, Folder 668)
    - A- January 1952-May 1953 (Box 13, Folder 669)
    - A- June 1953- December 1953 (Box 13, Folder 670)
    - B- January 1952-February 20, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 671)
    - B- February 25-April 15, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 672)
    - B- April 16- May 25, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 673)
    - B- May 26-June 1953 (Box 13, Folder 674)
    - B- July-August 1953 (Box 13, Folder 675)
    - B- September-November 1953 (Box 13, Folder 676)
    - B- December 1953; C- January 1953 (Box 13, Folder 677)
    - C- February-March 1953 (Box 13, Folder 678)
    - C- April-May 15, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 679)
    - C- May 19-July 10, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 680)
    - C- July 13-October 15, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 681)
    - C- October 16-December 1953; D- January 1953 (Box 13, Folder 682)
    - D- February-April 20, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 683)
    - D- April 21-July 1953 (Box 14, Folder 684)
    - D- August-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 685)
    - E- January-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 686)
    - F- January-June 15, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 687)
    - F- June 16-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 688)
    - G- January-April 1953 (Box 14, Folder 689)
    - G- May-September 1953 (Box 14, Folder 690)
    - G- October-December 1953; H- January 1953 (Box 14, Folder 691)
    - H- February-March 1953 (Box 14, Folder 692)
    - H- April-May 1953 (Box 14, Folder 693)
    - H- June-July 1953 (Box 14, Folder 694)
    - H- August-October 1953 (Box 14, Folder 695)
    - H- November-December 1953; I- January-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 696)
    - J- January-June 1953 (Box 14, Folder 697)
    - J- July-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 698)
    - K- January-April 1953 (Box 14, Folder 699)
    - K- May-September 1953 (Box 14, Folder 700)
    - K- October-December 1953; L- January-February 1953 (Box 14, Folder 701)
    - L- February 11-April 15, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 702)
    - L- April 16-June 1953 (Box 14, Folder 703)
    - L- July-October 15, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 704)
    - L- October 16-December 1953; M- January-February 10, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 705)
    - M- February 11-March 20, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 706)
    - M- March 23-April 1953 (Box 14, Folder 707)
    - M- May-June 10, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 708)
    - M- June 11-July 1953 (Box 14, Folder 709)
    - M- August-October 15, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 710)
    - M- October 16-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 711)
    - N- January-May 1953 (Box 14, Folder 712)
    - N- June-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 713)
    - O- January-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 714)
    - P- January-March 20, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 715)
    - P- March 23-June 19, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 716)
    - P- June 22-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 717)
    - Q- January-December 1953; R- January-March 1953 (Box 14, Folder 718)
    - R- April-July 10, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 719)
    - R- July 17-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 720)
    - S- January-February 16, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 721)
    - S- February 17-April 6, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 722)
    - S- April 7-May 20, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 723)
    - S- May 22-July 10, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 724)
    - S- July 13-October 15, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 725)
    - S- October 16-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 726)
    - T- January-April 15, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 727)
    - T- April 17-July 15, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 728)
    - T- July 17-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 729)
    - U- January-December 1953; V- January-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 730)
    - W- January-March 13, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 731)
    - W- March 16-May 1953 (Box 14, Folder 732)
    - W- June-August 1953 (Box 14, Folder 733)
    - W- September-December 1953; X, Y, Z- January-December 1953 (Box 14, Folder 734)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1954
    - A- January-March (Box 14, Folder 735)
    - A- April-June (Box 14, Folder 736)
    - A- July-December (Box 14, Folder 737)
    - B- January-February 20 (Box 14, Folder 738)
    - B- February 23-March (Box 14, Folder 739)
    - B- April-May 20 (Box 14, Folder 740)
    - B- May 21-July 20 (Box 14, Folder 741)
    - B- July 22-September (Box 14, Folder 742)
    - B- October-December (Box 14, Folder 743)
    - C- January-February (Box 14, Folder 744)
    - C- March-April (Box 14, Folder 745)
    - C- May-July 9 (Box 14, Folder 746)
    - C- July 12-September (Box 14, Folder 747)
    - C- October-December (Box 14, Folder 748)
    - D- January-March (Box 15, Folder 749)
    - D- April-June (Box 15, Folder 750)
    - D- July-December (Box 15, Folder 751)
    - E- January-December (Box 15, Folder 752)
    - F- January-April (Box 15, Folder 753)
    - F- May-December (Box 15, Folder 754)
    - G- January-March (Box 15, Folder 755)
    - G- April-July 20 (Box 15, Folder 756)
    - G- July 22-December (Box 15, Folder 757)
    - H- January-February 19 (Box 15, Folder 758)
    - H- February 23-March (Box 15, Folder 759)
    - H- April-May 5 (Box 15, Folder 760)
    - H- May 6-July 15 (Box 15, Folder 761)
    - H- July 16-September (Box 15, Folder 762)
    - H- October-December (Box 15, Folder 763)
    - I- January-December; J- January-April (Box 15, Folder 764)
    - J- May-December (Box 15, Folder 765)
    - K- January-March (Box 15, Folder 766)
    - K- April-July (Box 15, Folder 767)
    - K- August-December (Box 15, Folder 768)
    - L- January-March (Box 15, Folder 769)
    - L- April-June (Box 15, Folder 770)
    - L- July-December (Box 15, Folder 771)
    - M- January-February 10 (Box 15, Folder 772)
    - M- February 11-March 22 (Box 15, Folder 773)
    - M- March 23-April (Box 15, Folder 774)
    - M- May-June 15 (Box 15, Folder 775)
    - M- June 16-July (Box 15, Folder 776)
    - M- August-September (Box 15, Folder 777)
    - M- October-December (Box 15, Folder 778)
    - N- January-June (Box 15, Folder 779)
    - N- July-December (Box 15, Folder 780)
    - O- January-December (Box 15, Folder 781)
    - P- January-March (Box 15, Folder 782)
    - P- April-June (Box 15, Folder 783)
    - P- July-November 10 (Box 15, Folder 784)
    - P- November 13-December; Q- January-December; R- January-February 15 (Box 15, Folder 785)
    - R- February 16-April 12 (Box 15, Folder 786)
    - R- April 13-July (Box 15, Folder 787)
    - R- August-December (Box 15, Folder 788)
    - S- January-February 19 (Box 15, Folder 789)
    - S- February 23-April 5 (Box 15, Folder 790)
    - S- April 6-June 4 (Box 15, Folder 791)
    - S- June 7-July 15 (Box 15, Folder 792)
    - S- July 16-September 25 (Box 15, Folder 793)
    - S- September 27-November 15 (Box 15, Folder 794)
    - S- November 18-December; T- January-March 15 (Box 15, Folder 795)
    - T- March 16-June (Box 15, Folder 796)
    - T- July-December (Box 15, Folder 797)
    - U- January-December; V- January-December (Box 15, Folder 798)
    - W- January-February (Box 15, Folder 799)
    - W- March-April 15 (Box 15, Folder 800)
    - W- April 16-June 15 (Box 15, Folder 801)
    - W- June 16-August (Box 15, Folder 802)
    - W- September-November (Box 15, Folder 803)
    - W- December; XYZ- January-December (Box 15, Folder 804)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1955
    - A- January-May (Box 15, Folder 805)
    - A- June-December (Box 15, Folder 806)
    - B- January-February (Box 15, Folder 807)
    - B- March-April 15 (Box 15, Folder 808)
    - B- April 18-May (Box 15, Folder 809)
    - B- June-July 20 (Box 15, Folder 810)
    - B- July 21-October (Box 15, Folder 811)
    - B- November-December (Box 15, Folder 812)
    - C- January-March 17 (Box 16, Folder 813)
    - C- March 21-May (Box 16, Folder 813)
    - C- June-August (Box 16, Folder 814)
    - C- September-December (Box 16, Folder 815)
    - D- January-May (Box 16, Folder 816)
    - D- June-December (Box 16, Folder 817)
    - E- January-December (Box 16, Folder 818)
    - F- January-April (Box 16, Folder 819)
    - F- May-December (Box 16, Folder 820)
    - G- January-April (Box 16, Folder 821)
    - G- May-December (Box 16, Folder 822)
    - H- January-February (Box 16, Folder 823)
    - H- March-April (Box 16, Folder 824)
    - H- May-July (Box 16, Folder 825)
    - H- August-December (Box 16, Folder 826)